{
    "1": {
        "question" : "Who was the captain of the Enterprise D?",
        "answer" : "b",
        "a" : "Wllliam Riker",
        "b" : "Jean Luc Picard",
        "c" : "James T. Kirk",
        "d" : "Spock",
        "e" : "None of the above"
    },
    "2": {
        "question" : "What was different about the Enterprise D?",
        "answer" : "d",
        "a" : "It could go warp 10",
        "b" : "It carried no weapons",
        "c" : "Impervious to Klingon weapons",
        "d" : "The saucer section could separate",
        "e" : "None of the above"
    },
    "3": {
        "question" : "What separates the Federation from Romulon space?",
        "answer" : "c",
        "a" : "A energy field",
        "b" : "Sector D",
        "c" : "The Neutral Zone",
        "d" : "Klingon Empire",
        "e" : "None of the above"
    },
    "4": {
        "question" : "What instrument does Commander William Riker play?",
        "answer" : "b",
        "a" : "Saxophone",
        "b" : "Trombone",
        "c" : "Wooden Flute",
        "d" : "Guitar",
        "e" : "Banjo"
    },
    "5": {
        "question" : "What instrument does the Captain learn to play, which ends up being decades of experience, during the course of the show?",
        "answer" : "c",
        "a" : "Clarinet",
        "b" : "Piano",
        "c" : "Wooden Flute",
        "d" : "Violin",
        "e" : "Saxaphone"
    },
    "6": {
        "question" : "In the first episode, what does Captain Picard ask Commander Riker to help him with?",
        "answer" : "b",
        "a" : "Monitoring the mood of the crew",
        "b" : "His image with children",
        "c" : "Solving a murder mystery",
        "d" : "Help him learn the names of the crew",
        "e" : "Understanding how the engines work"
    },
    "7": {
        "question" : "When Patrick Stewart asked Gene Roddenberry to give him more information on the character of Captain Jean-Luc Picard, Roddenberry sent him what book(s)?",
        "answer" : "c",
        "a" : "The Pirate Captain by Kerry Lynee",
        "b" : "The Story of Robin Hood and his Merrie Men by Lawrence Edward Watkin",
        "c" : "The Time Machine by H.G. Wells",
        "d" : "Horatio Hornblower by C.S. Forester",
        "e" : "Moby Dick by Herman Melville"
    },
    "8": {
        "question" : "What is the name of Dr. Beverly Crusher's son?",
        "answer" : "e",
        "a" : "William Crusher",
        "b" : "Will Riker",
        "c" : "Wil Wheaton",
        "d" : "Will Crusher",
        "e" : "Wesley Crusher"
    },
    "9": {
        "question" : "The bridge that Scotty recreated on the holodeck of Enteprise NCC 1701 - D was from which ship?",
        "answer" : "e",
        "a" : "Excelsior Refit Class Enterprise NCC 1701 - B",
        "b" : "Constituion Refit Class Enterprise NCC 1701 - Refit",
        "c" : "Ambassador Class Enterprise NCC 1701 - C",
        "d" : "Constitution Refit Class Enterprise NCC 1701 - A",
        "e" : "Constituion Class Enterprise NCC 1701"
    },
    "10": {
        "question" : "What is the song Data is trying to whistle in Season 1 on the holodeck?",
        "answer" : "d",
        "a" : "Row Row Row You Boat",
        "b" : "Taps",
        "c" : "Comin' Round the Mountain",
        "d" : "Pop Goes the Weasel",
        "e" : "Johnny Comes Marching Home"
    },
    "11": {
        "question" : "What did Data name his cat?",
        "answer" : "a",
        "a" : "Spot",
        "b" : "The General",
        "c" : "Lal",
        "d" : "Mittens",
        "e" : "Fluffy"
    }
}
